{
  "category": "link",
  "sections": [
    {
      "title": "Talk",
      "chats": [
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[British warship HMS Diamond blasts Iran-backed drones with Sea Viper missiles](https://youtu.be/T2P8CYm3I5E?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.161Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Sadhguru - Stop Being Dead Serious About Life](https://youtu.be/cfsuose6EaM)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Inspirational Thinkers: Charles Bukowski's Philosophy On Life... Be Real](https://youtu.be/ddwqTc_l3UU)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[When You Feel Like A Stranger In The World - Alan Watts On The Mystic Experience](https://youtu.be/DRmgh-CE0K8)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[How to overcome sexual desires and hormones hijacking ?](https://youtu.be/sWHS9ebbENQ)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Aaron Clarey: Life without the opposite sex](https://youtu.be/lZDPoiGKEpU)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[All men PAY: the more she likes you, the bigger the discount](https://youtu.be/6r8H_ij8DPU)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Why SEX WORKERS HATE MEN](https://youtu.be/YWMV-8zTUFM)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Men Should Pay For Kitty](https://youtu.be/CAOnIpofkXE)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Joe Rogan and Dan Bilzerian: Is It Bad To Pay For Sex?](https://youtu.be/xY4_GdOGLho)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Do we need a Theory of Everything?](https://youtu.be/mdu9KvLxHFg)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Synthetic Sentience: Can Artificial Intelligence become conscious? | Joscha Bach | CCC #37c3](https://youtu.be/Ms96Py8p8Jg)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Joscha Bach Λ Karl Friston: Ai, Death, Self, God, Consciousness](https://youtu.be/CcQMYNi9a2w?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Dostoevsky's Genius Life Philosophy](https://youtu.be/vEFlbz9SSEU?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[We Worry About Problems We Don't Even Have | Eastern Philosophy](https://youtu.be/XyzIX87zuTw?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[So, you're a lone wolf?](https://youtu.be/-45QPC6f_T8?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[When Life is Meaningless (And Why We Feel Worthless)](https://youtu.be/8Twa6BN6jmU?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[You're Not Supposed To Be Happy](https://youtu.be/EVUDGqcrerQ?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[What To Do If Nothing Makes You Happy Anymore](https://youtu.be/2Hu27xr06VI?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[If You're Feeling Behind In Life](https://youtu.be/kgSr6eIUqko?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[The Lebowski theorem - @SimulationSeries](https://youtu.be/yXCO3MDBk04?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Linus Torvalds \"Nothing better than C\"](https://youtu.be/CYvJPra7Ebk?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Peoples Addictions To Sexual Pleasures - Alan Watts](https://youtu.be/TUkoS6RhlLg?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[US - Trump on Putin: \"we've got a lot of killers. You think our country's so innocent?\"](https://youtu.be/G8-VB-XkjKQ?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Jonathan Blow $100k in debt on his first game company](https://youtu.be/JZ-OoYkHHD0?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Thoughts on Finding Love | Coffee With Hampton](https://youtu.be/jelML5grkSs?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[How Do We Manage Loneliness?](https://youtu.be/Q6nX9sJz2Ys?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[The Dilemma Of Loneliness](https://youtu.be/AcXf5rJ13x8?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Noam Chomsky - The Alternative to Capitalism](https://youtu.be/RUzquEya6Lw?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Why capitalism fails | Richard Wolff and Lex Fridman](https://youtu.be/XthLoLZZKbM?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[CYBERPUNK 2077 Phantom Liberty Endings Explained: Is This the Only Right Ending?](https://youtu.be/Q4j-LCaM3hI?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[The decline of play | Peter Gray | TEDxNavesink](https://youtu.be/Bg-GEzM7iTk?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[The Mating Crisis: Why the Dating Market Is Doomed](https://youtu.be/txRSxee7gDo?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Stanisław Lem vs. Grzegorz Braun](https://youtu.be/37K-P77tZXo?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Man With 200 IQ Gives Theory on Reality (CTMU Explained)](https://youtu.be/LeDm633T-_U?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[\"Don't be corrupt, It doesn't matter if you die for it.\" - Jiddu Krishnamurti](https://youtu.be/b4h7G4ZQ8fQ?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Become Ok With Being Alone (Episode 76)](https://youtu.be/y7M-CjE2XLg?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Why I'm committed to staying single](https://youtu.be/adp_VOhD98Q?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Looks matter more than Personality (The Cold Truth)](https://youtu.be/E7rekEt5whE?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Do Attractive People Have Better Personalities? | Beauty Psychology](https://youtu.be/nvbfbBzSgPI?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Why Bill Gates Is Pushing for Global Digital IDs and Taking Over America’s Farmland – Seamus Bruner](https://youtu.be/OHKlt-ik95Q?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Ramana Maharshi's Final Teaching | Can You Handle the Truth?](https://youtu.be/hddHUVsVO-w?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Audio | J. Krishnamurti - Rishi Valley 1983 - School Discussion (Students) 4 - Why do images...](https://youtu.be/YArhkfYBAwM?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[The REAL reason why \"NOBODY WANTS TO WORK ANYMORE\"](https://youtu.be/4M2_-3-Rqsk?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[I don't want to work full-time: Freedom, part-time jobs, income & future anxieties](https://youtu.be/cjwwa4HSaPU?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[The Mind Behind Windows: Dave Cutler](https://youtu.be/xi1Lq79mLeE?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[The Minds Behind Windows: Raymond Chen](https://youtu.be/-vJQv4rgHYE?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[This is What Happens After Fiat Fails](https://youtu.be/FWycTVZQWmQ?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[How Your Wealth Is Being Robbed And What You Can Do About It | Jeff Booth](https://youtu.be/QTlG6a5GI3s?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[John Mearsheimer: Israel-Palestine, Russia-Ukraine, China, NATO, and WW3 | Lex Fridman Podcast #401](https://youtu.be/r4wLXNydzeY?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[CAN YOU BELIEVE I FORGOT SOMETHING???](https://youtu.be/R-xSGfNP1E4?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Alan Watts - Freedom From Illusion](https://youtu.be/G-Ctjx7qXRE?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[The Rules to the Game of Life - Alan Watts](https://youtu.be/4vv93azMkDE?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[U.G. Krishnamurti - Why Follow Spiritual LIFE | NO GURU | NO Enlightenment | NO Freedom By UG](https://youtu.be/udzIsWyl4WI?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Life Is Impermanent | J. Krishnamurti](https://youtu.be/iOB6nojuwVc?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Krishnamurti. We Have No Love](https://youtu.be/q5n1MsD17bY?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[NO Freedom And NO Such Thing As Art Of Anything | UG Krishnamurti](https://youtu.be/6ZtwGVdeRkY?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Joscha Bach: Most humans have very little agency over their beliefs](https://youtu.be/VN9T4QYRRl0?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Richard Burton - the Greatest Poem in the English Language.mpg](https://youtu.be/fDNCEp8Utjo?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[The Harder You Try, The Worse It Gets - The Philosophy of Fyodor Dostoevsky](https://youtu.be/F9kfiUhmRO8?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[What Does This Life Really Mean? - Jim Carrey](https://youtu.be/wTblbYqQQag?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[San Francisco Streets](https://youtu.be/URfCwT3UQy4?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[https://youtu.be/URfCwT3UQy4?feature=shared](https://youtu.be/wwymOW-5mE0?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[U G Krishnamurti - Discussion On Everything | UG Krishnamurti VIDEOS](https://youtu.be/epgDWLPAu00?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Think correctly about MONEY - J.Krishnamurti](https://youtu.be/QU9jgazFsrU?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Inspirational Thinkers: From Lost Soul To Laughing Heart (Bukowski On Life)](https://youtu.be/qEFEU8eMhmI?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[The Philosophy of Charles Bukowski | Starving for Your Freedom!](https://youtu.be/3zKl2qdqSJU?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Finding Something to Live and Die For | The Philosophy of Viktor Frankl](https://youtu.be/JX-8-IYhQKk?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[How can an isolated entity love? | Krishnamurti](https://youtu.be/Ct48Pf0ipmo?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Elades ilma rahata / Living Without Money](https://youtu.be/QDKuAtfcCZE?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Krishnamurti - Most people are occupied with jobs (English subtitles)](https://youtu.be/4FHU_friuis?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Dubai Is Everything Wrong With Society](https://youtu.be/qJqqw1S8nHI?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[You never face your loneliness | J. Krishnamurti](https://youtu.be/HOBsym9IeO0?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[What is loneliness? | Krishnamurti](https://youtu.be/pWWxLeosUPE?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Remain with loneliness | Krishnamurti](https://youtu.be/eu5ZGdt8uUY?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Your Boss Is Not Your Friend- Self-help Singh](https://youtu.be/loPPLyG__jY?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Don't expect recognition: why no one cares about your thing](https://youtu.be/_uFInF1eRZM?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[The genius of George Carlin](https://youtu.be/NxeDKqbRre0?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[George Carlin - I Don't Care](https://youtu.be/lcZAFU5bV_Q?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Do nothing, the art of work in 2022.](https://youtu.be/GRjyCD_lhfQ?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[A Guided Meditation on the Body, Space, and Awareness with Yongey Mingyur Rinpoche](https://youtu.be/5GSeWdjyr1c?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Carl Sagan - Pale Blue Dot](https://youtu.be/wupToqz1e2g?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Carl Sagan's Pale Blue Dot OFFICIAL](https://youtu.be/GO5FwsblpT8?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Chomsky on having a job](https://youtu.be/iR1jzExZ9T0?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[How To Have Fun In Life](https://youtu.be/86QJseeARV0?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[The Global Monetary Order Is Broken, Says Lyn Alden](https://youtu.be/JsSXo3o-Nrc?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[We Are All Actors - Alan Watts On The Game We Play](https://youtu.be/sfjdXHvonAs?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[America’s Labor Economy is 100% Fake | GMBN](https://youtu.be/uHpDpzNkMiQ?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[What do you mean by 'Give your life to understand life'? | J. Krishnamurti](https://youtu.be/73JCinTbYLw?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Why should one meditate? | Krishnamurti](https://youtu.be/2D2IPDRPvFY?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Question: What do you think about the Buddha? | Krishnamurti](https://youtu.be/hOqPo1j-uFI?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Life is precious | Krishnamurti](https://youtu.be/o4rSCAGhESU?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Alan Watts ~ How To Enjoy Life](https://youtu.be/O6sZzy3R-60?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Alan Watts on Hermits and Outcasts](https://youtu.be/EK5RaHpI4M8?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Who are you? | J. Krishnamurti](https://youtu.be/_uTZoQ6_h0Q?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[The purpose of art is to capture conscious states - @TheoriesofEverything](https://youtu.be/iyhJ9BEjink?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Tim Dillon - BEST rant EVER!](https://youtu.be/cSvTR7rSLY0?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[The Path To Enlightenment By ALAN WATTS](https://youtu.be/42sCIsiXs2s?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[What is enlightenment? | J. Krishnamurti](https://youtu.be/WhVkmmlw6Nw?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[This One Stupid Human Idea Is Destroying The Planet | Warning All Life Will Stop To Exist | Sadhguru](https://youtu.be/xFaHxDkonS8?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Joscha Bach—How to Stop Worrying and Love AI](https://youtu.be/YeXHQts3xYM?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[What If the World Was A Single Country?](https://youtu.be/lEhyAOunq28?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[We STOPPED global warming once (by accident)... can we do it again?](https://youtu.be/FPhyY5VZo0E?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Feeling Like a Failure at 40 // How to Stop Feeling Behind in Life](https://youtu.be/-u6RpFHHCvc?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[4 Steps to Self-sufficient Living and Leaving Society](https://youtu.be/pu-Zgq1KyGA?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[The Illusion of Freedom - Are You Really Free To Do What You Want?](https://youtu.be/ANlPOFwgimc?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Forget the Great Reset. Embrace the Great Escape.](https://youtu.be/Cd0OeC6Syd4?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Why You Should IGNORE Job \"Requirements\" & APPLY ANYWAY! | #grindreel](https://youtu.be/NaPezvkzl8U?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Iraq Vet: Don’t Join the U.S. Military](https://youtu.be/P3cpGTZQx44?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[How do you receive something that's beyond the mind? | J. Krishnamurti](https://youtu.be/hTkBA3fuvio?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[DIVIDE & RULE - The Plan of The 1% to Make You DISPOSABLE - Vandana Shiva](https://youtu.be/f9lq-uBdxg8?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[How to reach enlightenment | Joscha Bach and Lex Fridman](https://youtu.be/zhHch_Qu2sk?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Meditation is about controlling attention - @lexfridman](https://youtu.be/TvswnpAcO0A?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Psychologist Explains Why “The Male Sex Drive Is A Tragedy”](https://youtu.be/8vNNehCn8Ac?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Don't Get Married](https://www.youtube.com/live/98pFjmL21dQ?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Request-Only Losers Go Into Debt](https://youtu.be/fRfr01bfnIk?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Alan Watts on conforming to society](https://youtu.be/KjSwsww5SfQ?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Alan Watts | A Scholar's Point of View](https://youtu.be/d8-L3sC4NoU?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[The Most Legendary Programmers Of All Time](https://youtu.be/KnAEIEnnvAQ?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Do Humans Have Free Will, Or Are We Programmed By Society? | Joscha Bach | Big Think](https://youtu.be/KUOW6Bgwleo?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[The TRUTH is a psyop... faking outrage and virtue for money.](https://youtu.be/Ox9wSYb86OY?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[AI, Consciousness, Science, Art & Understanding - Joscha Bach](https://youtu.be/noScrzeEh4o?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Children who eat too much sugar are developing diseases only alcoholics used to get](https://youtu.be/gKkebjyKAn8?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[The five-day workweek was made up. What if we changed it?](https://youtu.be/hn5-FIkFq0I?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[WHY YOU HAVE TO CUT OUT 99.9% OF EVERYBODY YOU KNOW | DAN RESPONDS TO BULLSHIT](https://youtu.be/mFmLoYjmV9Y?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[If You Try To Hold On To Life You Will Lose It | Alan Watts](https://youtu.be/djdl3qmBbdc?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Terry Crews: Men don't see women as 'all the way human'](https://youtu.be/GibE058a4P0?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Putin asks Sberbank CEO when he will be replaced by AI](https://youtu.be/c8q6P_HfIBE?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Christopher Walken On \"We Are Born Alone. We Die Alone…\"](https://youtu.be/rYayeUMsD28?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Stop Trying to Learn How to Code.. It's NOT Worth It! ..as a self taught programmer](https://youtu.be/gq2AglURmiY?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Not Everyone Should Code or 10 Signs That Programming Is Not For You](https://youtu.be/dTsjy7a0VYc?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Why is coding so hard...](https://youtu.be/TAAXwrgd1U8?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[LITERATURE - Edward Gibbon](https://youtu.be/tY3sQwiqniI?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[U.G. Krishnamurti - Identity Depends on Fear](https://youtu.be/2FMoiZB_ClA?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Charles Bukowski on drinking 🍷](https://youtu.be/ENpcgPaPDeM?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Bukowski on people](https://youtu.be/LJw4Xd952_g?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[J. Krishnamurti & David Bohm - Brockwood Park 1980 - The Ending of Time - Conversation 15](https://youtu.be/aU5WXHdFaic?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Charles Bukowski: Why most Writers are Boring.](https://youtu.be/fo9CQT3hXu8?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[People Are Pointless - The Philosophy of Charles Bukowski](https://youtu.be/g5GhdZIG5kQ?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Escapism vs. Community (Into the Wild Analysis)](https://youtu.be/Vlz3BmiJr6I?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[The Fantasy of Ultimate Purpose – How Our Entertainment Reveals Our Deepest Desire](https://youtu.be/sSLb3COkAHg?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[The Philosophy of Mr. Nobody – How To Make Meaningful Choices](https://youtu.be/ANUunK6kiqU?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Is programming dead? | Stephen Wolfram and Lex Fridman](https://youtu.be/uD353DeOM-4?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Bukowski~People Are Not Free!](https://youtu.be/qup1BLNFDWU?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Nietzsche - Follow No One, Trust Yourself](https://youtu.be/e-k7b8Zmh70?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Marcus Aurelius - Stop Caring What People Think](https://youtu.be/PVKaK5Xt6TI?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[George Carlin Politicians](https://youtu.be/07w9K2XR3f0?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[George Carlin Lost Faith in Humanity | Late Night with Conan O’Brien](https://youtu.be/-BdBF8c07cs?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[George Carlin — I Just Don't Care](https://youtu.be/kAQS7BzRW_k?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Why Most Humans are Worthless](https://youtu.be/g8WsUjlhRVQ?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[The Ugly Truth About Mother Teresa](https://youtu.be/-UY-KkPY3vc?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Joscha Bach: Life, Intelligence, Consciousness, AI & the Future of Humans | Lex Fridman Podcast #392](https://youtu.be/e8qJsk1j2zE?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[A Market Driven U.S. Dollar Downgrade Is the Real Threat - Ep 910](https://www.youtube.com/live/XTBCz9kOSUc?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[LK-99 BUSTED!!!](https://youtu.be/p3hubvTsf3Y?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[A Jr Dev For Life?? | Prime Reacts](https://youtu.be/61lVNkvk9AU?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Jim Rickards: Western Economies About To Slam Into A BRICS Wall?](https://youtu.be/88pP53lcBwQ?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Lyn Alden: Money Is ‘Broken’, Markets Face ‘Rerating’ Risks](https://youtu.be/dXujV7P_hZc?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Stop Trying to Get It And You'll Have It - Alan Watts on Life's Meaning](https://youtu.be/LSs-s9E9xDI?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[The Harder You Look, The Less You'll See - Alan Watts' Profound Revelation](https://youtu.be/_GonTIAbhHg?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Control - Alan Watts](https://youtu.be/7kfe9nJUP2E?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[J. Krishnamurti - Brockwood Park 1980 - Public Talk 3 - What is the relationship between the...](https://youtu.be/meZdaRLeTSk?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[The Meaning of Anti-Work](https://youtu.be/lP0nBIO1Qo8?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Charles Bukowski - Anti work](https://youtu.be/CRrSRLIgLnE?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Escaping the Rat Race: What School Failed to Teach You About Money.](https://youtu.be/9RJpIqD8MGg?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Overcoming depression: The self is a fiction | Joscha Bach and Lex Fridman](https://youtu.be/7hqfZ5sPcGw?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Joscha: Computational Meta-Psychology](https://youtu.be/WRdJCFEqFTU?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Is the universe a computer? with Joscha Bach](https://youtu.be/UvtYTClRSes?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Chris Hedges - Reality of Psychopaths](https://youtu.be/sU0AA31NcDw?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Dr. Peter Kreeft | The 10 Books Nobody Should Be Allowed to Die Without Reading](https://youtu.be/bLm5RggbhlE?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Why People Hurt People | Chris Hedges](https://youtu.be/kHlnNn4QKEk?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Carlos Castaneda’s #Quotes and #aphorisms. Shaman don Juan’s wisdom](https://youtu.be/73I6LIvLUos?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Reinvent your Life - Charles Bukowski](https://youtu.be/9CQIl0P4piQ?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[All I’m Offering is the Truth | The Philosophy of the Matrix](https://youtu.be/X0W6CX-uHhk?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Joscha Bach: The Six Stages of Development of the Self | The Western Confusion about Consciousness](https://youtu.be/oOI3nPKUeRc?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Programmers Aren't Productive Anymore - Jonathan Blow](https://youtu.be/bZ6pA--F3D4?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Always Be Silent In Five Situation | Albert Einstein | Inspirational Quotes](https://youtu.be/SrCYcFeinaM?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[What Does Post-Capitalism Look Like? | Yanis Varoufakis](https://youtu.be/T8sAHG1JQPY?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[The Cult Of The Self | Chris Hedges](https://youtu.be/QZIVQ8ExqEY?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[The Wild Route: Leaving Work and Home for a Forest Life | NBC Left Field](https://youtu.be/5yh0j6zMWCI?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Role of Emotion in the Mind (Joscha Bach) | AI Podcast Clips](https://youtu.be/hFoItZlYARI?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Joscha Bach: What Can AI Tell Us about the Human Mind?](https://youtu.be/g3auFru7IvI?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Multiway Systems as Models to Understand Mind and Universe - a Conversation with Stephen Wolfram](https://youtu.be/O_5e_WSNedE?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[“We are in a debt trap” - Nouriel Roubini on 10 ‘megathreats’ to our world and how to stop them](https://youtu.be/ADh6QTp8798?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[A Lesson From Socrates That Will Change The Way You Think](https://youtu.be/yH86jaBQ0F4?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Advice for young people: Don't study economics | Steve Keen and Lex Fridman](https://youtu.be/mFgXz0R5k98?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[J R R Tolkien Quotes - The Wisdom of Tolkien and The Lord of The rings](https://youtu.be/1TFCyhKVkyI?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Life is Like Music - Alan Watts](https://youtu.be/gTLYiOg9C6M?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Nobody can help you | J. Krishnamurti](https://youtu.be/zu4yvjTDVjM?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[NO ONE IS COMING TO SAVE YOU | DAVID GOGGINS](https://youtu.be/3R-1FodDQTM?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[On relationships - UG Krishnamurti](https://youtu.be/oZcOzQVMTFs?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Guy Ritchie \"You Must Be The Master of Your Own Kingdom\" - The Joe Rogan Experience](https://youtu.be/rd3yeX1-SaM?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[U.G. Krishnamurti - Dead Things Cannot Help Us Understand Anything](https://youtu.be/4ebv8U97xL4?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Tom Hardy and Gene Simmons - Even when you have it all, it's good to be alone](https://youtu.be/66M7JTgqXa0?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Money, happiness and eternal life - Greed (2/2) | DW Documentary](https://youtu.be/qLSt4VtmT5M?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[The Cheaper Your Pleasures, The Richer You’ll Be | Minimalist Philosophy](https://youtu.be/Oswc-jAgwgo?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Joscha Bach: Artificial Consciousness and the Nature of Reality | Lex Fridman Podcast #101](https://youtu.be/P-2P3MSZrBM?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[A JOB is MODERN DAY SLAVERY](https://youtu.be/y4-fIZWIT3s?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Jeff Booth: Building A Better Future With Bitcoin](https://youtu.be/TBCb82xaDeM?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[#82 - Dr. JOSCHA BACH - Digital Physics, DL and Consciousness [UNPLUGGED]](https://youtu.be/LgwjcqhkOA4?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Society's Trap - Joe Rogan](https://youtu.be/a0jNLEEDsDw?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Our civilization may not exist for long (Joscha Bach) | AI Podcast Clips](https://youtu.be/jhIVarkAXas?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[\"He that increaseth knowledge increaseth sorrow.\"](https://youtu.be/eqgWLg34BWQ?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[The tower of Babel - @SingularityFM](https://youtu.be/2KoaJSvOfkc?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[How To Own Yourself - Carl Jung (Jungian Philosophy)](https://youtu.be/nHn3EgxLiYw?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Men want Success and Sex while Women want... #alberteinstine #motivation #quote #short #usa #shorts](https://youtu.be/udTmCa0hxzc?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[How To Be Sane In An Insane World | Featuring J. Krishnamurti and Alan Watts](https://youtu.be/_z5aSoQI2Y4?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Charles Bukowski: The Slavery of the 9 to 5](https://youtu.be/vV5ARyuxpow?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Taxi Driver, Purposeless Jobs and Alienation](https://youtu.be/p0Fzip47Lu4?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Joyless economies: Unregulated capitalism, slavery, and feudalism | Yanis Varoufakis | Big Think](https://youtu.be/dEi7XUlyr_A?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[What If We Just...Stopped Working?](https://youtu.be/2i0RrGx_GrE?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[How Capitalism Ruined Work](https://youtu.be/3aQgN_7oX0Q?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Your Needs Are Fake and Your Job Is Pointless](https://youtu.be/DcSdT3JQEG8?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Michael Levin Λ Joscha Bach: Collective Intelligence](https://youtu.be/kgMFnfB5E_A?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Intelligence and Intellect: What's The Difference - Shekhar Kapur with Sadhguru](https://youtu.be/mBt75tpJ07I?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Sadhguru: If You Remind this to you, You will never become Serious! | Story of Islamic Sufi Master](https://youtu.be/rkntJQnAhpA?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[EP72 Joscha Bach on Minds, Machines & Magic](https://youtu.be/x0bHMn68kL8?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Lose Yourself - An Inspirational Poem By Rumi](https://youtu.be/JNKBoq8avCA?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[15 Rumi Poems in English](https://youtu.be/0Kj3-Yf-Qi0?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Jeff Booth: Bitcoin Replaces the Entire System](https://youtu.be/jeHodRch11Y?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[IF, Rudyard Kipling's poem, recited by Sir Michael Caine](https://youtu.be/EEFMVIfl2UY?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Is all money just a ponzi scheme? | Vicki Robin | Big Think | Big Think](https://youtu.be/XVFYAsvUyVg?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[MASS PSYCHOSIS - How an Entire Population Becomes MENTALLY ILL](https://youtu.be/09maaUaRT4M?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[The Benefit of Living With No Purpose - Alan Watts](https://youtu.be/dx4yW0mjezw?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Life Is Worth Losing - Dumb Americans - George Carlin](https://youtu.be/KLODGhEyLvk?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Michael Saylor: Win With Bitcoin](https://youtu.be/j3h9s9jcx_I?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Alia Bhatt Gets Scared As Mahesh Bhatt Gets ANGRY on Media While Answering Questions On Depression](https://youtu.be/rkjOjKwaqRQ?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Jim Keller: Abstraction Layers from the Atom to the Data Center | AI Podcast Clips](https://youtu.be/7bLeQFhPwzk?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Zen Master Gu Ja - Just eat, sleep and shit](https://youtu.be/7HHFH2oQxNA?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Seth Rogen Explains Why Life Is MUCH better without Kids!](https://youtu.be/hrOTC3sxwQA?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Neil Gershenfeld: Self-Replicating Robots and the Future of Fabrication | Lex Fridman Podcast #380](https://youtu.be/YDjOS0VHEr4?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[poverty and 9 to 5 work slavery](https://youtu.be/wsLZMwnRRQs?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "['Know Thyself' | Krishnamurti & Eric Robson](https://youtu.be/T15-4B6zMuA?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Stephen Wolfram: ChatGPT and the Nature of Truth, Reality & Computation | Lex Fridman Podcast #376](https://youtu.be/PdE-waSx-d8?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Find your talent and stick to it | Krishnamurti #shorts](https://youtu.be/TfyXnyK6ty8?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[J. Krishnamurti - San Diego 1974 - Conversation 18 - Meditation and the sacred mind](https://youtu.be/HMyX2FXE9S4?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Life is Pointless and that's the Beauty of it!](https://youtu.be/5amjKlpbR2A?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[On the demands of society and a life of total freedom | J. Krishnamurti](https://youtu.be/FNo09qBVOdY?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[No Birth, No Death | Teaching by Thich Nhat Hanh](https://youtu.be/AwoTsoeIfcQ?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[J. Krishnamurti - Brockwood Park 1976 - The Transformation of Man - 1 - Are we aware that we](https://youtu.be/Dvtxu1QJHeQ?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[J. Krishnamurti - Brockwood Park 1978 - School Discussion 1 - Can you give equal...](https://youtu.be/ChOszAnHD7w?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Alan Watts | Human Consciousness | Education for Non-Entity (full)](https://youtu.be/t2mIZU4nJo0?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Give up - UG Krishnamurti](https://youtu.be/EGPxlBbP30A?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[There's Nothing To Do But Watch it - Alan Watts on Depression](https://youtu.be/1Q_snggTLnQ?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Everything Is Nothing - Alan Watts on Nothingness](https://youtu.be/0Ayx6m2Qct4?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Money Maxims](https://youtu.be/4-LJuPDlGWw?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[U.G. Krishnamurti Dismantles Everything You Thought You Believed by Alphonse Perillo](https://youtu.be/r_vdrfp8Yjo?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Stuck With Misery | UG Krishnamurti](https://youtu.be/IN9EvIFbR0c?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Think correctly about MONEY - J.Krishnamurti](https://youtu.be/QU9jgazFsrU?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Try Not To Get A Job | Alan Watts & J. Krishnamurti](https://youtu.be/zPY5NIQsz2g?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Jiddhu Krishnamurti on 9 to 5 jobs.](https://youtu.be/-nDwfdfCSMA?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Why all this effort? | Krishnamurti](https://youtu.be/HzX2XMruqFw?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[What is the right relationship to money? | J. Krishnamurti](https://youtu.be/Ep_g41H-6nE?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[What is the right way to earn a living? | J. Krishnamurti](https://youtu.be/iIqVJaF4Gig?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[MEN DON'T NEED WOMEN! (It's Time To Wake Up...)](https://youtu.be/mRmqv1VM3_o?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Men and women DON'T NEED each other anymore: the consequences of replacing necessity with desire](https://youtu.be/QP1LstGtYrk?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[J. Krishnamurti - Ojai 1984 - Public Talk 2 - What is wrong with pleasure?](https://youtu.be/0nHrhOsiZcw?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Robocop Rogue City - Streets of Fire](https://youtu.be/7xcxqglm3vQ?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[The myth of Sisyphus - Alex Gendler](https://youtu.be/q4pDUxth5fQ?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[gRPC Service with .NET 7](https://youtu.be/Rqz9XiSqH3E?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Corksoakers - SNL](https://youtu.be/Deqx-Xb-yHY?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Colonel Angus Comes Home - SNL](https://youtu.be/3l2oi-X8P38?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Badger Up His Butt - Saturday Night Live](https://youtu.be/dr2uYO5B6y8?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Pranksters: Prankster Larry - SNL](https://youtu.be/jORviU2oyMQ?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[The Gold Watch - Pulp Fiction (7/12) Movie CLIP (1994) HD](https://youtu.be/YFtHjV4c4uw?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[\"Two Little Mice\" speech by Christopher Walken](https://youtu.be/51lFmdChOA0?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Your Brain Wants You To Have Sex. Here's How That Works. | Better | NBC News](https://youtu.be/4DJ0F-UFF4g?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Is life meaningless? And other absurd questions - Nina Medvinskaya](https://youtu.be/vPtzpjC7TF4?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Silent Hill 2 ost (full album)](https://youtu.be/QFvt2cNSOaM?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Guillermo at the Oscars](https://youtu.be/QGjLWxOKels?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Pirates of the Caribbean Ultimate Cut](https://youtu.be/h5oR88Xhwyc?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Cruel Cruel World - Willie Nelson](https://youtu.be/TzwDN1D5i_M?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Red Dead Redemption 2 Official Soundtrack (Latest Update) | HD](https://youtu.be/McnMsFwZlvA?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[There is nothing to learn about yourself | Krishnamurti](https://youtu.be/FWuD1Sh1GYY?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Anime Quote | Ayanokouji Kiyotaka -All people are nothing but tools](https://youtu.be/TEWgesTUYZc?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Financial ‘Endgame’ In Sight, Economic Reset Looms | Willem Middelkoop](https://youtu.be/ZtI2ZQCZ3NM?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[We Don’t Want Pleasure; We Just Want the Pain to End](https://youtu.be/5QavLGNj9as?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[You don't fit in, so stop trying to.](https://youtu.be/7Wj8FQzHNdg?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Ricky Gervais Offensive Jokes (Armageddon)](https://youtu.be/_67LfYjIIJw?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[I've read over 100 coding books. Here's what I learned](https://youtu.be/AZpv9cb-H-M?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[5 Books That Can Change A Developer’s Career](https://youtu.be/RfOYWeu5pGk?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[The KEY To Thinking Like a Programmer (Fix This Or Keep Struggling)](https://youtu.be/vrmKwQ-JPTA?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[The Most Legendary Programmers Of All Time](https://youtu.be/KnAEIEnnvAQ?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Is marriage dying? | Richard Reeves](https://youtu.be/ALZQu9x96Jg?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Boomers Got the Vax - SNL](https://youtu.be/2hekDuCBxCc?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Boeing: Last Week Tonight with John Oliver (HBO)](https://youtu.be/Q8oCilY4szc?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[15 Years Writing C++ - Advice for new programmers](https://youtu.be/37VZu3b045k?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Humans Are A Unique Type Of Pest](https://youtu.be/YRiZOBOZTE0?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[The Sanity of 'Madness'](https://youtu.be/tYfQSyDuriA?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Krishnamurti - Most people are occupied with jobs (English subtitles)](https://youtu.be/4FHU_friuis?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[The Surest Way out of Misery | Arthur Schopenhauer](https://youtu.be/R50MI4VXtOI?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Joe Rogan: \"If You Want To Kill The Most Things, Become A Vegan\"](https://youtu.be/i_BcYSTYErE?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[Dolly Shuts Down Patronising Interview In Style](https://youtu.be/If-oWqUYzlQ?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[INSANE Jane Fonda Want's To Put White Men In Jail](https://youtu.be/pKxdrwokyAI?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  },
  {
    "indexTitle": "",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "[SKIBIDI TOILET Explained](https://youtu.be/48Zmr30hQW8?feature=shared)",
    "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:19:04.162Z"
  }
]
    }
  ]
}